League for Industrial Democracy Pamphlets 5266
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- L [folder 4 of 7], Publication (Box 1, Folder 12d)
  - Item 76: The L. I. D. and Its Activities, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12d)
  - Item 77: Taking a New Look ta the LID, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12d)
  - Item 78: Taking a New Look ta the LID, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12d)
  - Item 79: Taking a New Look ta the LID, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12d)
  - Item 80: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12d)
  - Item 81: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12d)
  - Item 82: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12d)
  - Item 83: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12d)
  - Item 84: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12d)
  - Item 85: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12d)
  - Item 86: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12d)
  - Item 87: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12d)
  - Item 88: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12d)
  - Item 89: Correspondence, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12d)
  - Item 90: How America Lives: A Handbook of Industrial Facts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12d)
  - Item 91: Forty-Five Years of Social Education, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12d)
  - Item 92: Postwar Planning for Peace and Full Employment, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12d)
- L [folder 5 of 7], Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 1: Freedom and the Welfare State: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 2: Needed: A Moral Awakening in America: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 3: A Program for Labor And Progressives: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 4: America in the Depression, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 5: British Labor as Government And as Opposition, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 6: British Labors Rise to Power, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 7: Consumers Cooperation; A Social Interpretation And the Consumers Cooperative Movement: A Factual Survey, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 8: Federal Government And Functional Democracy, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 9: How America Lives: A Handbook of Industrial Facts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 10: How America Lives: A Handbook of Industrial Facts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 11: Incentives Under Capitalism And Socialism, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 12: Labor Governments at Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 13: Our Changing Industrial Incentives, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 14: Public Ownership Here And Abroad, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 15: Putting the Constitution to Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 16: Recent Developments in the American Labor Movement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 17: The Role of the Races in Our Future Civilization, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 18: Roads to Freedom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 19: Socialism in the United States: A Brief History, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 20: The New Capitalism And the Socialist, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 21: The Third Freedom: Freedom From Want: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 22: Toward A Farmer-Labor Party, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 23: Toward Nationalization of Industry, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 24: Unemployment And Its Remedies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 25: Unemployment And Its Remedies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 26: Unemployment Insurance Plans Abroad, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 27: World Cooperation And Social Progress: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 28: The Denial of Civil Liberties in the Coal Fields, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 29: The Campus Strikes Against War, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 30: Karl Marx An Essay, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 31: The Underground Struggle In Germany, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 32: The Atomic Age: suicide--slavery or social planning, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 33: Why the C. I. O, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 34: Labor, Machines And Depressions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 35: Why We Have Depressions And Recessions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 36: The Future of Capitalism and Socialism In America: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 37: Swedens Labor Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 38: The Railroads Versus Public Interest, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 39: Monopoly And Big Business, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 40: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 41: Maximum Production: Warfare and Welfare, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 42: The Middle Class and Organized Labor, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 43: America in the Depression, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 44: British Labor as Government And as Opposition, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 45: British Labors Rise to Power, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 46: Freedom and the Welfare State: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 47: How America Lives: A Handbook of Industrial Facts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 48: Incentives Under Capitalism And Socialism, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 49: Labor Governments at Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 50: Maximum Production: Warfare and Welfare, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 51: Needed: A Moral Awakening in America: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 52: Needed: A Moral Awakening in America: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 53: The New Capitalism And the Socialist, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 54: Our Changing Industrial Incentives, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 55: A Program for Labor And Progressives: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 56: A Program for Labor And Progressives: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 57: Public Ownership Here And Abroad, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 58: Recent Developments in the American Labor Movement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 59: Recent Developments in the American Labor Movement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 60: Roads to Freedom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 61: Socialism in the United States: A Brief History, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 62: The Third Freedom: Freedom From Want: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 63: Toward A Farmer-Labor Party, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 64: Toward Nationalization of Industry, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 65: Unemployment And Its Remedies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 66: Unemployment And Its Remedies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 67: World Cooperation And Social Progress: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 68: Karl Marx An Essay, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 69: The Underground Struggle In Germany, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 70: The Atomic Age: suicide--slavery or social planning, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 71: Why the C. I. O, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 72: Why We Have Depressions And Recessions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 73: Swedens Labor Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 74: Monopoly And Big Business, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 75: The Middle Class and Organized Labor, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 76: The L. I. D. and Its Activities, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 77: Taking a New Look ta the LID, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 78: Taking a New Look ta the LID, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 79: Taking a New Look ta the LID, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 80: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 81: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 82: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 83: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 84: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 85: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 86: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 87: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 88: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 89: Correspondence, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 90: How America Lives: A Handbook of Industrial Facts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 91: Forty-Five Years of Social Education, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
  - Item 92: Postwar Planning for Peace and Full Employment, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12e)
- L [folder 6 of 7], Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 1: Freedom and the Welfare State: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 2: Needed: A Moral Awakening in America: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 3: A Program for Labor And Progressives: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 4: America in the Depression, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 5: British Labor as Government And as Opposition, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 6: British Labors Rise to Power, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 7: Consumers Cooperation; A Social Interpretation And the Consumers Cooperative Movement: A Factual Survey, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 8: Federal Government And Functional Democracy, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 9: How America Lives: A Handbook of Industrial Facts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 10: How America Lives: A Handbook of Industrial Facts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 11: Incentives Under Capitalism And Socialism, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 12: Labor Governments at Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 13: Our Changing Industrial Incentives, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 14: Public Ownership Here And Abroad, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 15: Putting the Constitution to Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 16: Recent Developments in the American Labor Movement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 17: The Role of the Races in Our Future Civilization, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 18: Roads to Freedom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 19: Socialism in the United States: A Brief History, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 20: The New Capitalism And the Socialist, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 21: The Third Freedom: Freedom From Want: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 22: Toward A Farmer-Labor Party, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 23: Toward Nationalization of Industry, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 24: Unemployment And Its Remedies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 25: Unemployment And Its Remedies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 26: Unemployment Insurance Plans Abroad, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 27: World Cooperation And Social Progress: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 28: The Denial of Civil Liberties in the Coal Fields, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 29: The Campus Strikes Against War, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 30: Karl Marx An Essay, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 31: The Underground Struggle In Germany, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 32: The Atomic Age: suicide--slavery or social planning, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 33: Why the C. I. O, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 34: Labor, Machines And Depressions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 35: Why We Have Depressions And Recessions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 36: The Future of Capitalism and Socialism In America: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 37: Swedens Labor Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 38: The Railroads Versus Public Interest, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 39: Monopoly And Big Business, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 40: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 41: Maximum Production: Warfare and Welfare, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 42: The Middle Class and Organized Labor, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 43: America in the Depression, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 44: British Labor as Government And as Opposition, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 45: British Labors Rise to Power, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 46: Freedom and the Welfare State: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 47: How America Lives: A Handbook of Industrial Facts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 48: Incentives Under Capitalism And Socialism, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 49: Labor Governments at Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 50: Maximum Production: Warfare and Welfare, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 51: Needed: A Moral Awakening in America: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 52: Needed: A Moral Awakening in America: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 53: The New Capitalism And the Socialist, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 54: Our Changing Industrial Incentives, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 55: A Program for Labor And Progressives: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 56: A Program for Labor And Progressives: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 57: Public Ownership Here And Abroad, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 58: Recent Developments in the American Labor Movement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 59: Recent Developments in the American Labor Movement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 60: Roads to Freedom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 61: Socialism in the United States: A Brief History, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 62: The Third Freedom: Freedom From Want: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 63: Toward A Farmer-Labor Party, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 64: Toward Nationalization of Industry, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 65: Unemployment And Its Remedies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 66: Unemployment And Its Remedies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 67: World Cooperation And Social Progress: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 68: Karl Marx An Essay, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 69: The Underground Struggle In Germany, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 70: The Atomic Age: suicide--slavery or social planning, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 71: Why the C. I. O, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 72: Why We Have Depressions And Recessions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 73: Swedens Labor Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 74: Monopoly And Big Business, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 75: The Middle Class and Organized Labor, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 76: The L. I. D. and Its Activities, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 77: Taking a New Look ta the LID, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 78: Taking a New Look ta the LID, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 79: Taking a New Look ta the LID, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 80: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 81: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 82: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 83: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 84: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 85: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 86: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 87: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 88: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 89: Correspondence, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 90: How America Lives: A Handbook of Industrial Facts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 91: Forty-Five Years of Social Education, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
  - Item 92: Postwar Planning for Peace and Full Employment, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12f)
- L [folder 7 of 7], Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 1: Freedom and the Welfare State: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 2: Needed: A Moral Awakening in America: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 3: A Program for Labor And Progressives: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 4: America in the Depression, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 5: British Labor as Government And as Opposition, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 6: British Labors Rise to Power, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 7: Consumers Cooperation; A Social Interpretation And the Consumers Cooperative Movement: A Factual Survey, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 8: Federal Government And Functional Democracy, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 9: How America Lives: A Handbook of Industrial Facts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 10: How America Lives: A Handbook of Industrial Facts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 11: Incentives Under Capitalism And Socialism, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 12: Labor Governments at Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 13: Our Changing Industrial Incentives, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 14: Public Ownership Here And Abroad, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 15: Putting the Constitution to Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 16: Recent Developments in the American Labor Movement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 17: The Role of the Races in Our Future Civilization, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 18: Roads to Freedom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 19: Socialism in the United States: A Brief History, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 20: The New Capitalism And the Socialist, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 21: The Third Freedom: Freedom From Want: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 22: Toward A Farmer-Labor Party, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 23: Toward Nationalization of Industry, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 24: Unemployment And Its Remedies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 25: Unemployment And Its Remedies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 26: Unemployment Insurance Plans Abroad, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 27: World Cooperation And Social Progress: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 28: The Denial of Civil Liberties in the Coal Fields, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 29: The Campus Strikes Against War, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 30: Karl Marx An Essay, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 31: The Underground Struggle In Germany, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 32: The Atomic Age: suicide--slavery or social planning, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 33: Why the C. I. O, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 34: Labor, Machines And Depressions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 35: Why We Have Depressions And Recessions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 36: The Future of Capitalism and Socialism In America: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 37: Swedens Labor Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 38: The Railroads Versus Public Interest, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 39: Monopoly And Big Business, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 40: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 41: Maximum Production: Warfare and Welfare, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 42: The Middle Class and Organized Labor, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 43: America in the Depression, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 44: British Labor as Government And as Opposition, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 45: British Labors Rise to Power, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 46: Freedom and the Welfare State: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 47: How America Lives: A Handbook of Industrial Facts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 48: Incentives Under Capitalism And Socialism, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 49: Labor Governments at Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 50: Maximum Production: Warfare and Welfare, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 51: Needed: A Moral Awakening in America: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 52: Needed: A Moral Awakening in America: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 53: The New Capitalism And the Socialist, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 54: Our Changing Industrial Incentives, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 55: A Program for Labor And Progressives: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 56: A Program for Labor And Progressives: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 57: Public Ownership Here And Abroad, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 58: Recent Developments in the American Labor Movement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 59: Recent Developments in the American Labor Movement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 60: Roads to Freedom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 61: Socialism in the United States: A Brief History, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 62: The Third Freedom: Freedom From Want: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 63: Toward A Farmer-Labor Party, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 64: Toward Nationalization of Industry, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 65: Unemployment And Its Remedies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 66: Unemployment And Its Remedies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 67: World Cooperation And Social Progress: A symposium, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 68: Karl Marx An Essay, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 69: The Underground Struggle In Germany, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 70: The Atomic Age: suicide--slavery or social planning, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 71: Why the C. I. O, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 72: Why We Have Depressions And Recessions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 73: Swedens Labor Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 74: Monopoly And Big Business, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 75: The Middle Class and Organized Labor, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 76: The L. I. D. and Its Activities, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 77: Taking a New Look ta the LID, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 78: Taking a New Look ta the LID, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 79: Taking a New Look ta the LID, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 80: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 81: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)